{
    "id": "33b81365401e4476a475c0dc3b9e9f5d",
    "title": "Identify The Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She took her daughter to the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Simple past",
                "Past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will always remember this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present perfect",
                "Simple future"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They asked me to wait.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple past",
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been studying since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present continuous",
                "Present perfect",
                "Present perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have finished the task assigned to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect",
                "Simple past"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Who broke the window?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple past",
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What were you doing then?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present continuous",
                "Past continuous",
                "Future continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who gave you the information?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Simple past",
                "Simple future"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He had forgotten to take his umbrella.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect",
                "Past perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This time tomorrow I will be playing with my friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple future",
                "Future continuous",
                "Future perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They will have gone to bed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present continuous",
                "Future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She stays with her grandparents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Simple past",
                "Simple future"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am working on a new project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present continuous",
                "Past continuous",
                "Present perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}